{
"quiz1": [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "questionType": "true_false",
    "questionText": "RAM stands for Random Access Memory",
    "correctAnswer": "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "questionType": "true_false",
    "questionText": "Java is an Object Oriented programming language",
    "correctAnswer": "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "questionType": "text_input",
    "questionText": "What the programming languages used for cpp files? (make sure to Capitalize)",
    "correctAnswer": "C Plus Plus",
    "explanation": "cpp is an acronym for C Plus PLus"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "questionType": "multiple_choice",
    "questionText": "Which of these is the HTML tag for making text bold?",
    "correctAnswer": "<b>",
    "options": ["<p>", "<bold>", "<b>", "<div>"],
    "explanation": "<bold> is not an html tag, and the other tags have different purposes, so it must be <b>"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "questionType": "text_input",
    "questionText": "What does CPU stand for? (make sure the capitalize)",
    "correctAnswer": "Central Processing Unit",
    "explanation": "CPU is an acronym for Central Processing Unit as it processes most data in the computer"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "questionType": "multiple_choice",
    "questionText": "What Operating System is developed and maintained by Microsoft?",
    "correctAnswer": "Windows",
    "options": ["Windows", "MacOS", "Linux", "Android"],
    "explanation": "Windows is owned by microsoft, while the others are owned by Apple, Linus Torvalds, and Google respectively"
  },
  {
"id": 6,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "6. Which is not a Java data type?",
"correctAnswer": "decimal",
"options": ["String", "int", "double", "decimal"],
"explanation": "Floats and doubles store decimal
values, but decimal itself is not a data type; String and int
are also both valid data types."
},
{
"id": 7,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "7. _______________ is credited with
being the very first computer programmer. (Full name,
please)",
"correctAnswer": "Ada Lovelace",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "Mathematician & writer Ada Lovelace
(1815-1852) wrote the world's first algorithm to the
Analytical Machine. The very first computer programmer
was a woman!"
},
{
"id": 8,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "8. Which OS is developed & used by
Apple Inc.?",
"correctAnswer": "iOS",
"options": ["Unix", "iOS", "Windows", "Ubuntu"],
"explanation": "macOS is Apple's operating system for
personal computers & workstations; iOS is a system for
mobile devices."
},
{
"id": 9,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "9. Which of the following are object-
oriented languages?",
"correctAnswer": ["Python","C++", "Ruby"],
"options": ["Python", "C", "C++", "Ruby"],
"explanation": "C is an imperative procedural
language; it does not use classes, inheritance,
polymorphism, or other features of OOP."
},
{
"id": 10,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "10. GIF stands for ________
Interchange Format. (Please capitalize)",
"correctAnswer": "Graphics",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "GIF stands for Graphics Interchange
Format."
},
{
"id": 11,
"questionType": "multi_text_input",
"questionTextBefore":"11. GUI stands for ",
"questionTextBetween":" User ",
"questionTextAfter":".",
"correctAnswer": ["Graphical", "Interface"],
"answerFieldId1":"answer_to_first_blank",
"answerFieldId2":"answer_to_second_blank",
"explanation": "GUI stands for Graphical User
Interface."
},
{
"id": 12,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "12. A binary system uses powers of
_____.",
"correctAnswer": "2",
"options": ["4", "2", "16", "8"],
"explanation": "As indicated by the prefix bi-, binary
systems use powers of 2."
},
{
"id": 13,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "13. Which of the following are
functions of an operating system?",
"correctAnswer": ["I/O management","Job scheduling",
"Memory management"],
"options": ["I/O management", "Database
management", "Job scheduling", "Memory management"],
"explanation": "Database management is the
responsibility of a DBMS, not an operating system.
Operating systems do handle I/O management, job
scheduling & memory management."
},
{
"id": 14,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "14. Which of the following is the
ascending order of data hierarchy?",
"correctAnswer": "Bit-Byte-Field-Record-File-
Database",
"options": ["Bit-Byte-Field-Record-File-Database",
"Field-Byte-Bit-Record-Database-File", "Bit-Byte-
Record-Field-File-Database", "Byte-Bit-Record-Field-
File-Database"],
"explanation": "Bits make up bytes, which make fields,
which compose records, which together create files,
which ultimately form databases."
},
{
"id": 15,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "15. SQL stands for Standard _______
Language.",
"correctAnswer": "Query",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "SQL stands for Standard Query
Language"
},
{
"id": 16,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "16. A virus is a computer __________.",
"correctAnswer": "Program",
"options": ["File", "Network", "Program", "Database"],
"explanation": "A virus is a typically destructive
PROGRAM that replicates itself by modifying other
computer programs & inserting its own code."
},
{
"id": 17,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "17. Which of the following operations
are performed on RAM?",
"correctAnswer": ["Read and write"],
"options": ["Read", "Write & edit", "Read and write", "It
depends on the user"],
"explanation": "Both read & write operations can be
performed on RAM."
},
{
"id": 18,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "18. Python requires the use of ;'s at
the end of lines of code.",
"correctAnswer": "False",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "Unlike a language like Java, Python
DOES NOT require the use of ;'s to end lines of code."
},
{
"id": 19,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "19. Hash maps/hash tables store key-
value pairs.",
"correctAnswer": "True",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "Data IS inserted into hash maps using
key-value pairs."
}
  ],
  "quiz2": [
    {
"id": 0,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "20. This is used to find the length of
a Java ArrayList.",
"correctAnswer": ".size()",
"options": [".length", ".size()", ".length()",
".lengthOf()"],
"explanation": "The .size() method is used to
determine the length of Java ArrayLists; .length is used
for Arrays."
},

    {
"id": 1,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "1. Select all valid Java loops.",
"correctAnswer": ["Do-while","While", "For"],
"options": ["Do-while", "If", "While", "For"],
"explanation": "Do-while, white, and for loops are all
valid in Java; if STATEMENTS are not loops."
},
{
"id": 2,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "2. What does CSS stand for?",
"correctAnswer": "Cascading Style Sheet",
"options": ["Cascading Style Sheet", "Color and Style
Sheet", "Cascade Stylesheet", "None of the above"],
"explanation": "CSS stands for Cascading Style
Sheet."
},
{
"id": 3,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "3. HTML determines the content of
a webpage.",
"correctAnswer": "True",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "HTML DOES outline the content of a
webpage - CSS styles it, and JS adds functionality."
},
{
"id": 4,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "4. 1024 bits is equal to _______
bytes.",
"correctAnswer": "128",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "1024 bits is equal to 128 bytes.
(There are 8 bits in each byte)"
},
{
"id": 5,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "5. Select the command line/terminal
command that allows you to navigate up one directory.",
"correctAnswer": "cd ..",
"options": ["cd /", "cd ~", "cd ..", "cd -"],
"explanation": "cd .. is the command used to
navigate up one directory. The others are valid commands
but have other uses."
},
{
"id": 6,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "6. Select all valid methods of tree
traversal.",
"correctAnswer": ["Inorder","Preorder", "Postorder"],
"options": ["Inorder", "Reorder", "Preorder",
"Postorder"],
"explanation": "Reorder is not a form of tree traversal;
the 3 others are all valid."
},
{
"id": 7,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "7. Which of these is referred to as
the 'brain' of the computer?",
"correctAnswer": "Central Processing Unit",
"options": ["Hard Drive", "Central Processing Unit",
"Database", "System Software"],
"explanation": "As the 'brain of the computer', the
CPU retreives & executes instructions."
},
{
"id": 8,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "8. The SQL COMBINE clause is used
to combine tables based on a shared column.",
"correctAnswer": "False",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "The JOIN clause is what's used to
combine tables based on a shared column."
},
{
"id": 9,
"questionType": "multi_text_input",
"questionTextBefore":"9. Alan ",
"questionTextBetween":"'s cryptoanalytical machine
'the bombe' broke ",
"questionTextAfter":", Nazi Germany's cipher device.
(Please capitalize)",
"correctAnswer": ["Turing", "Enigma"],
"answerFieldId1":"answer_to_first_blank",
"answerFieldId2":"answer_to_second_blank",
"explanation": "Alan Turing is credited with designing
the machine that broke Enigma."
},
{
"id": 10,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "10. Check all output devices.",
"correctAnswer": ["Speaker","Monitor"],
"options": ["Keyboard", "Speaker", "Monitor",
"Mouse"],
"explanation": "Speakers & monitors are output
devices, while keyboards & mice are input devices."
},
{
"id": 11,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "11. What does DOM stand for?",
"correctAnswer": "Document Object Model",
"options": ["Document Objective Model", "Document
Output Model", "Document Object Model", "Document
Object Modeling"],
"explanation": "DOM stands for Document Object
Model."
},
{
"id": 12,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "12. This animal shares it's name with
a Python module used to create vector graphics.",
"correctAnswer": "Turtle",
"options": ["Lizard", "Snake", "Frog", "Turtle"],
"explanation": "Turtle is the name of the Python
module used as a drawingboard to create graphics."
},
{
"id": 13,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "13. Flexbox is a CSS layout model.",
"correctAnswer": "True",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "The Flexible Box Model (aka. Flexbox)
IS a CSS layout model."
},
{
"id": 14,
"questionType": "text_input",
"questionText": "14. How many iterations are there to
this Java for loop? : for(int i = 1; i < 20; i++){...}",
"correctAnswer": "19",
"answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
"explanation": "If this loop went from i = 0 to i < 20 it
would have 20 iterations; it instead starts at 1, so there
are 19."
},
{
"id": 15,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "15. == can be used to compare the
content of Java Strings for equality.",
"correctAnswer": "False",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "Java Strings should NOT be
compared using ==, but by using .equals() intead."
},
{
"id": 16,
"questionType": "multiple_choice",
"questionText": "16. Which of the following is correct
syntax for printing 'Hello World' in Java?",
"correctAnswer": "System.out.println('Hello World');",
"options": ["print('Hello World');",
"System.out.println('Hello World');", "System.out('Hello
World');", "echo('Hello World');"],
"explanation": "The correct syntax for this Java print
statement is: System.out.println('Hello World');"
},
{
"id": 17,
"questionType": "true_false",
"questionText": "17. Java is short for JavaScript.",
"correctAnswer": "False",
"options": ["True", "False"],
"explanation": "Java is NOT short for Javascript. The
two languages are completely different."
},
{
"id": 18,
"questionType": "checkbox",
"questionText": "18. Check all valid Java variable
names.",
"correctAnswer":
["myName","myName1","my_name"],
"options": ["myName", "1myName", "myName1",
"my_name"],
"explanation": "Variable names cannot start with
numbers; therefore, all of the chocies are valid except for
1myName."
},
{
"id": 19,
"questionType": "multi_text_input",
"questionTextBefore":"19. RDBMS stand for ",
"questionTextBetween":" ",
"questionTextAfter":" Management System. (Please
capitalize)",
"correctAnswer": ["Relational", "Database"],
"answerFieldId1":"answer_to_first_blank",
"answerFieldId2":"answer_to_second_blank",
"explanation": "RDBS stands for Relational Database
Management System."
}
  ]
}
